const zodiac = [
{
    "question": "Aries",
    "choices": ["March 21-April 19","April 20-May 20","May 21-June 20"],
    "correct":"March 21-April 19",
},
{
    "question": "Taurus",
    "choices": ["March 21-April 19","April 20-May 20","June 21-July 22"],
    "correct": "April 20-May 20",
},
{
    "question": "Gemini",
    "choices": ["March 21-April 19","May 21-June 20","October 23-November 21"],
    "correct": "May 21-June 20",
},
{
    "question": "Cancer",
    "choices": ["July 23-August 22","June 21-July 22","December 22-January 19"],
    "correct": "June 21-July 22",
},
{
    "question": "Leo",
    "choices": ["July 23-August 22","August 23-September 22","March 21-April 19"],
    "correct": "July 23-August 22",
},
{
    "question": "Virgo",
    "choices": ["September 23-October 22","August 23-September 22","October 23-November 21"],
    "correct": "August 23-September 22",
},
{
    "question": "Libra",
    "choices": ["October 23-November 21","Feb 19-March 20","September 23-October 22"],
    "correct": "September 23-October 22",
},
{
    "question": "Scorpio",
    "choices": ["October 23-November 21","November 22-December 21","August 23-September 22"],
    "correct": "October 23-November 21",
},
{
    "question": "Sagittarius",
    "choices": ["November 22-December 21","December 22-January 19","Feb 19-March 20"],
    "correct":"November 22-December 21",
},
{
    "question": "Capricorn",
    "choices": ["July 23-August 22","December 22-January 19","Jan 20-Feb 18"],
    "correct": "December 22-January 19",
},
{
    "question": "Aquarius",
    "choices": ["December 22-January 19","Jan 20-Feb 18","Feb 19-March 20"],
    "correct": "Jan 20-Feb 18",
},
{
    "question": "Pisces",
    "choices": ["Feb 19-March 20","Jan 20-Feb 18","November 22-December 21"],
    "correct":"Feb 19-March 20",
},
];

const stars = [
{
    "question": "Aries",
    "choices": ["Mars","Venus","Mercur"],
    "correct": "Mars",
},
{
    "question": "Taurus",
    "choices": ["Venus","Mars","Mercur"],
    "correct": "Venus",
},
{
    "question": "Gemini",
    "choices": ["Mercur","Moon","Mercur"],
    "correct": "Mercur",
},
{
    "question": "Cancer",
    "choices": ["Moon","Mercur","Venus"],
    "correct": "Moon",
},
{
    "question": "Leo",
    "choices": ["Sun","Venus","Mars"],
    "correct": "Sun",
},
{
    "question": "Virgo",
    "choices": ["Mercur","Sun","Venus"],
    "correct": "Mercur",
},
{
    "question": "Libra",
    "choices": ["Venus","Mercur","Moon"],
    "correct": "Venus",
},
{
    "question": "Scorpio",
    "choices": ["Mars","Venus","Jupiter"],
    "correct": "Mars",
},
{
    "question": "Sagittarius",
    "choices": ["Jupiter","Saturn","Mars"],
    "correct": "Jupiter",
},
{
    "question": "Capricorn",
    "choices": ["Saturn","Uranus","Jupiter"],
    "correct": "Saturn",
},
{
    "question": "Aquarius",
    "choices": ["Uranus","Saturn","Neptun"],
    "correct": "Uranus",
},
{
    "question": "Pisces",
    "choices": ["Neptun","Uranus","Saturn"],
    "correct": "Neptun",
},
]